{
  "first":{
    "question":"How do you choose a suitable restaurant?",
    "background":"background_1",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_confused",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["I'm looking for a suitable using phone","my acquaintance recommended","I already know where I'm going","I go down the street to ask all those who come for an opinion"],
    "I'm looking for a suitable using phone":"saapuminen",
    "my acquaintance recommended":"saapuminen",
    "I already know where I'm going":"saapuminen",
    "I go down the street to ask all those who come for an opinion":"saapuminen",
    "I'm looking for a suitable using phoneColor":"green",
    "my acquaintance recommendedColor":"green",
    "I already know where I'm goingColor":"green",
    "I go down the street to ask all those who come for an opinionColor":"yellow"},
  "saapuminen":{
    "question":"does the restaurant have table control?",
    "background":"background_5",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_surprised",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["yes","no","all the same I leave because I don't like people","I don't know so I ask the waitress"],
    "yes":"ohjaus",
    "no":"menen",
    "all the same I leave because I don't like people":"null",
    "I don't know so I ask the waitress":"saapuminen",
    "yesColor":"green",
    "noColor":"green",
    "all the same I leave because I don't like peopleColor":"red",
    "I don't know so I ask the waitressColor":"green"},
  "ohjaus":{
    "question":"are you waiting for someone to direct you to the table?",
    "background":"background_5",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_uncomfortable",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["yes","no but I go to the table myself"],
    "yes":"haku",
    "no but I go to the table myself":"huomautus",
    "yesColor":"green",
    "no but I go to the table myselfColor":"red"},
  "menen":{
    "question":"you go to the table how do you let the waitress want to order?",
    "background":"background_5",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_uncomfortable",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["I look at the waitress questioningly","I try to gather as little attention as possible"],
    "I look at the waitress questioningly":"tilaus",
    "I try to gather as little attention as possible":"odotus",
    "I look at the waitress questioninglyColor":"green",
    "I try to gather as little attention as possibleColor":"yellow"},
  "haku":{
    "question":"the waitress comes and asks that you follow",
    "background":"background_5",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_uncomfortable",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["I follow to the table where the waitress directs me","I don't follow"],
    "I follow to the table where the waitress directs me":"tilaus",
    "I don't follow":"null",
    "I follow to the table where the waitress directs meColor":"green",
    "I don't followColor":"red"},
  "huomautus":{
    "question":"you will be reminded of how you are doing?",
    "background":"background_5",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_uncomfortable",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["I follow the instructions","I do as I please"],
    "I follow the instructions":"tilaus",
    "I do as I please":"null",
    "I follow the instructionsColor":"green",
    "I do as I pleaseColor":"red"},
  "tilaus":{
    "question":"the waiter will inquire about what you order.",
    "background":"background_5",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_surprised",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["I tell the order","I ask what she\/he recommends and then decide what to order","the contents of the barking menu"],
    "I tell the order":"tilattu",
    "I ask what she\/he recommends and then decide what to order":"tilattu",
    "the contents of the barking menu":"tilaus",
    "I tell the orderColor":"green",
    "I ask what she\/he recommends and then decide what to orderColor":"green",
    "the contents of the barking menuColor":"red"},
  "odotus":{
    "question":"the waitress will notice you after a long wait and will ask for an order.",
    "background":"background_5",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_surprised",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["barking waiter and slowness of service","I tell the order","I ask what she\/he recommends and then decide what to order","the contents of the barking menu"],
    "barking waiter and slowness of service":"odotus",
    "I tell the order":"tilattu",
    "I ask what she\/he recommends and then decide what to order":"tilattu",
    "the contents of the barking menu":"tilaus",
    "barking waiter and slowness of serviceColor":"red",
    "I tell the orderColor":"green",
    "I ask what she\/he recommends and then decide what to orderColor":"green",
    "the contents of the barking menuColor":"red"},
  "tilattu":{
    "question":"food comes to table how do you do?",
    "background":"background_5",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_happy",
    "fore":"fore_6",
    "answers":["I play with food an I leave","I eat matter-of-factly and wait for the waiter after that","I eat matter-of-factly and leave without paying","I eat and after that I go to pay for food at the counter"],
    "I play with food an I leave":"null",
    "I eat matter-of-factly and wait for the waiter after that":"syoty",
    "I eat matter-of-factly and leave without paying":"null",
    "I eat and after that I go to pay for food at the counter":"lahto",
    "I play with food an I leaveColor":"red",
    "I eat matter-of-factly and wait for the waiter after thatColor":"green",
    "I eat matter-of-factly and leave without payingColor":"red",
    "I eat and after that I go to pay for food at the counterColor":"green"},
  "syoty":{
    "question":"the waitress comes and cleans the table",
    "background":"background_5",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_happy",
    "fore":"fore_6",
    "answers":["you inquire about the bill","barking at everything","you still order dessert"],
    "you inquire about the bill":"maksettu",
    "barking at everything":"maksettu",
    "you still order dessert":"tilattu",
    "you inquire about the billColor":"green",
    "barking at everythingColor":"red",
    "you still order dessertColor":"green"},
  "maksettu":{
    "question":"after you pay you do what?",
    "background":"background_5",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_happy",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["I'm leaving","I go to the bathroom and leave","industry rampage"],
    "I'm leaving":"lahto",
    "I go to the bathroom and leave":"lahto",
    "industry rampage":"null",
    "I'm leavingColor":"green",
    "I go to the bathroom and leaveColor":"green",
    "industry rampageColor":"red"},
  "lahto":{
    "question":"you leave the restaurant how do you do?",
    "background":"background_5",
    "person":"character_6",
    "face":"face_happy",
    "fore":"null",
    "answers":["I will continue my journey","I will give feedback and continue my journey","I leave and bark at a restaurant bad for everyone"],
    "I will continue my journey":"null",
    "I will give feedback and continue my journey":"null",
    "I leave and bark at a restaurant bad for everyone":"null",
    "I will continue my journeyColor":"green",
    "I will give feedback and continue my journeyColor":"green",
    "I leave and bark at a restaurant bad for everyoneColor":"red"}
}